

Tristan Libeau

Professional Summary

I am a dedicated student who is currently studying Web Development as a part of a Bootcamp Program facilitated by the University of Sydney. My name is Tristan Libeau, my previous skill set that I have mastered over the past 10 years is within the field of Hospitality. I have found that my overall passion for Hospitality has dwindled and I have subsequently incurred an interest in computer hardware and software. My passion for technology as a whole initially derived from building Personal Computers for myself and some friends.

I began to find myself more intrigued and wished to learn more about the Software side of computing and this led to my interest in the field of Web Development and coding. There was something truly enticing about creating a program and the conceptual framework of interacting with a computer on the most fundamental level in order to create an application with intuitive and practical purpose. The more that I learn, the more passionate I become and my initial goal upon completion of my studies is to find a Job as a Junior Developer in a Software Company where I can begin to flourish as a Developer and to work on projects as apart of a large-scale team with a uniform

Work History

Accor Hotels - Sydney - Barista

Sydney, New South Wales

03/2021 - Current

- Maintained supply levels in counter and customer areas to meet typical demands.
- Prioritized drink requests while managing interruptions.
- Controlled line and crowd with quick, efficient service.

Bellucci Cucina, Sydney - Barista

06/2018 - 03/2021

- Quickly and accurately handled financial transactions of all types.
- Trained new employees on store policies and procedures.
- Remained knowledgeable about food industry trends and cultures.

★ tristan.libeau@gmail.com

0451962593

2009, Pyrmont, NSW

Website, Portfolio, Profiles

- https://tristanlibeau.github.io/Updated
 -Portfolio/index.html
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/tristanlibeau-78942a210/
- https://github.com/TristanLibeau

Skills

- Ability to Multitask
- Communication
- Leadership Skills
- Adaptability
- Ability to Work Under Pressure
- Front-End Skills: HTML, CSS
- User Research
- Responsive Web Design
- JavaScript

Cubecorp - Sydney - Real Estate Agent

03/2018 - 08/2019

- In charge of promoting and selling new off the plan project.
- House inspection.
- Showroom inspection.

Romolo Espresso Cucina - Sydney - Barista/Supervisor

08/2017 - 01/2018

- In charge of the floor.
- In charge of training new staff.
- Plan and improves menu with the manager regularly.
- Provided excellent customer service.

Sokyo - The Star Casino, Sydney - Bar Attendant (World Best bar qualified by Forbes)

02/2016 - 08/2017

- Monitored bar inventory and made notes for needed supplies when necessary.
- Built positive rapport with guests.
- Utilized excellent public speaking skills.

Harvest Buffet - The Star Casino, Sydney - Food and Beverage Attendant 09/2015 - 02/2016

- Maintained a neat, organized, and safe working environment.
- Performed all duties in accordance with Food Handling Procedures.
- Ensured sanitation and safety of units.

InterContinental, Sydney - Food and Beverage Attendant

March 2015 — September 2015.

- Responsible for the setup of the bar and the main floor.
- Performed all duties in accordance with Food & Beverage Handling Procedures.

Prince de Galles, a Luxury Collection Hotel, Paris - Waiter and Bartender March 2013 — January 2015.

- Cash Handling.
- Improved my knowledge of French wines.
- In charge of cocktails production.

Hôtel Barrière L'Hermitage, La Baule Escoublac-Bartender

07/2011 - 11/2012

- In charge of cocktails production, responsible for the set-up of the bar.
- Devised and implemented improvements concerning menus.
- In charge of orders from the suppliers.
- In charge of the stock take.

Education

Saint-Anne School

Saint-Nazaire, France
Barman Certification
//www.lycee-sainte-anne.fr/FR/index.awp

Saint-Anne School

Saint-Nazaire, France High School Certificate: Hospitality

Sydney University

Sydney, NSW Bootcamp Coding/Programing

Additional Information

• Full Driving License (Australian)